

# **PERSONAL DATA**

- warchol.tomasz.m@gmail.com
- **\** 733 142 210
- Kraków

# **SKILLS**

- CSS, HTML, Python
- English B2
- · Driving license category B
- Computer skills(Linux, MS Office, Windows, Jira, CRM, Zoom, Slack etc)
- · Repair of any hardware faults
- Knowledge of specialized FTS systems and services
- Knowledge of the computer structure

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- Teamwork
- Good manners
- Self-discipline
- · Logical and critical thinking
- · Flexibility and creativity
- · Resistance to stress
- Communicativeness
- Willingness to develop and learn
- · Positive attitude

# **TOMASZ WARCHOŁ**

## IT Support specialist, Helpdesk & Technical Support

My professional goal is satisfaction with learning and development in a challenging environment. Gaining new knowledge and skills in the field of IT. My motto is: If I can't do something, I'll learn it.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **TECHNICAL SUPPORT SPECIALIST**

Forward Thinking Systems

2021 - obecnie

- Assisting the client in solving technical problems
- Solving problems contained in Tickets
- Working on building Artificial Intelligence
- Evaluating requests for new features, bug reports and performances issues.

#### COMPUTER TECHNICIAN

2019 - 2020 🖣

**Events - Predator Thronos** 

• Support for the Predator Thronos game station at events

#### **TECHNIK VR**

2018 - 2021

**VR CAFE** 

- Taking care of VR equipment
- Introducing the best solutions for the client
- Repairing failures, introducing optimization, all technical aspects of Virtual Reality equipment
- · Testing games, and equipment
- Training employees
- Participation in board meetings

#### PROGRAMMER'S ASSISTANT

2017 - 2018

Łukasz Dubiel - Software Developer in Synerise

• Fixing bugs in the code, completing the code.

#### **OTHER**

Festival technician, Stage technique, Festival team.

Galicja Productions, Eventech, others. (Work on big festivals (Opener Festival, Orange Warsaw Festival, Kraków Live Music Festival, and many others) and concerts, stage technology, assembly, and disassembly, care for artists.)

Help in running a business Usługi Ogólnobudowlane, Prace Ziemne Andrzej Warchoł (Team

management, work on the construction site.)

# **EDUCATION**

Cracow University of Technology -Civil Engineering - Road Construction

2008 - 2013

Kazimierz Wielki School Complex No. 1 (Minsk Mazowiecki) Road Technical School, Road technician diploma 2004 - 2008

sonal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 2